# **Attapol Sinchalong**

Bath, United Kingdom nickattapol@gmail.com +447481932393 linkedin.com/in/attapolsinchalong

### **Personal profile**

MBA graduate with 5 years' international consultancy experience in sales and marketing modules working in multi-national teams. Strong analytical and problem solving skills, flexible and adaptable attitude. A capable team leader with a high level of integrity and proven ability to coach and develop team members.

### **Education**

09/2015 - 09/2016	University of Bath, Bath, United Kingdom
	Master of Business Administration (MBA)
	Dissertation: Risk management in the Tech startups
07/2016 - 07/2016	Florida International University, Miami, Florida
	Executive Certificate in International Business (Scholarship)
05/2007 - 05/2011	Thammasat University (SIIT), Bangkok, Thailand
	Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

### Experience

## 08/2013 - 07/2015 ExxonMobil IT, Bangkok, Thailand (Full-time)

### Functional Process Analyst

- Led team of six consultants to complete roll-out SAP projects for ExxonMobil and Esso companies in North Asia and South Pacific.
- Conducted analyzes and problem resolution, led status meetings and designed business blueprints in Order to Cash areas.
- Designed, developed and deployed SAP system changes and enhancements to improve quality of IT systems in Sales & Distribution and Transportation modules.
- Consulted and cooperated more than 80 business users gathering requirements, supporting QA and conducting training sessions.

# 12/2012 - 07/2013 PTT ICT Solutions Company Limited, Bangkok, Thailand (Full-time) Consultant

- Led team of three consultants to provide 24/7 support both SAP and non-SAP systems in PTT Global Chemical Sales and Marketing team.
- Designed, developed and implemented system changes,
   functionality specification, configuration, authorization matrix, SAP

- report, ABAP query to improve quality of IT systems in Sales & Distribution modules.
- Implemented new business process workflow to approve customer credit through mobile application based on the paperless office.

# 06/2011 - 11/2012 Atos, Bangkok, Thailand (Full-time)

## **Junior Consultant**

- Provided 1st line support for international customers: Siemens AG,
   Siemens Wind Power, OCS International Facilities Management
   Services (UK) and HMC Polymers Co., Ltd.
- Supported as Sales and Distribution Functional Consultant 3rd tier for all Siemens companies across Australia, ASEAN, China, Far East Asia, Indian subcontinent, Middle East Asia and Africa clusters.
- Recommended program enhancements to ensure smooth uninterrupted operations with high customer satisfaction.

# **Activities and Leadership**

- 2016 Google Online Marketing Challenge (GOMC) partnered with Age UK Bath & North East Somerset on creating AdWords online marketing campaign for their fundraising and volunteering activities. Role: Team Captain - Ranked: Needs Improvement
- 2007-2011 Vice President of the School of ICT, Thammasat University (SIIT)
- 2004-2008 committee member of Youth for Next Step, organized 7 charity events for disabled and disadvantaged people in Thailand.

### Certifications

- Google AdWords Search Certification
- Google Analytics Certification
- Coursera: English Common Law: Structure and Principles

### **Interests and Skills**

- Languages: Thai mother tongue and English fluent
- IT Skills: SAP, ABAP, SQL, R, SPSS, UC4batch, Microsoft Excel, Word, PowerPoint, Visio and Project
- Sports: football and badminton